<resources>
    <string name="app_name">7 Wonders</string>
    <string name="welcome">Which wonder do you want to visit?</string>
    <string name="b1">Machu Picchu</string>
    <string name="b2">Chichén Itzá</string>
    <string name="b3">Colosseum</string>
    <string name="b4">Taj Mahal</string>
    <string name="b5">Petra</string>
    <string name="b6">Great Wall</string>
    <string name="b7">Redeemer Christ</string>
    <string name="vista">Seeing Wonder</string>

    <string name="machu_picchu">Built before the 15th century, 80 kilometers northwest of Cusco (Peru),
    we find this masterpiece of Inca architecture and engineering.
    \n\nIt consists of three main structures:
        \n\t- ¨the Intihuatana¨.
        \n\t- the Temple of the Sun
        \n\t- Temple of the Three Windows.

        \n\nDeclared as one of the new seven wonders of the modern world on July 7, 2007.</string>

    <string name="chichen">Founded around 250 A.D., it is one of the main Mayan archaeological sites in the Yucatan Peninsula (Yucatan, Mexico).
    \nIt is an important and renowned vestige of the Mayan civilization.

    \n\nOn July 7, 2007 the Temple of Kukulcan located in Chichen Itza, was recognized as one of the new seven wonders of the modern world.</string>

    <string name="coliseum">Built between 70 and 80 A.D. it was an amphitheater from the time of the Roman Empire.
    \nLocated in the east of the Roman Forum.
    \n\nIt had a capacity for about 65,000 spectators. Those closest to the arena were those of higher social status. A
    as one ascended, the lower statuses were located.
    \n\nIt was used for almost five centuries.
    \n\nThe Colosseum was recognized as one of the new seven wonders of the modern world on July 7, 2007.</string>

    <string name="taj_mahal">Located in the city of Agra (India), it was built between 1631 and 1653.
    \n\nIt is an outstanding example of Mughal architecture. It combines elements of Islamic, Persian, Turkish and Indian architectural traditions.
    \n\nIt is constructed primarily of white marble. It is recognized as a symbol of love and beauty.
    \n\nOn July 7, 2007 it became one of the seven wonders of the modern world.  </string>

    <string name="petra">An ancient city located in southern Jordan, southeast of the Muet Sea and east of the Gulf of Aqaba.
    \nIt was the capital of the Nabataean Kingdom, an ancient Arab civilization between the 4th century BC and 2nd century AD.
    \n\nIt is known for its impressive rock-cut structures. The most famous facade is the Treasury (Al-Khazneh),
    carved into a rock wall and adorned with columns and sculptures.
    \n\nDeclared one of the new seven wonders of the modern world on July 7, 2007.</string>

    <string name="china">Construction began in the 3rd century B.C. during the Qin dynasty, although much of the wall we know today
        was built during the Ming dynasty (1368-1644).
    \nIt was built to protect the Chinese empire from invasions by nomadic tribes from the north such as the Mongols.
    \n\nIts length is approximately 21200 kilometers, although significant portions are in ruins or have disappeared over time.
    \n\nIt receives millions of visitors each year. It is a symbol of the greatness and strength of the ancient Chinese empire.</string>

    <string name="cris">Emblematic statue of Jesus Christ located at the top of Corcovado hill in Rio de Janeiro (Brazil).
    \nIt was built between 1922 and 1931. It has a height of 30 meters, from the base would be 38.
    \nIt has become a recognizable icon worldwide and is one of the main tourist destinations in Brazil.
    \n\nIt is an architectural and artistic masterpiece, both for its visual beauty and its spiritual and cultural significance.
    \n\nIt has been one of the seven wonders of the new world since July 7, 2007.</string>



</resources>